passiveincome2012.com 2016-03-21

# ElementalTrader » Privacy Policy

**What information do you collect automatically?**

For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name but not the e-mail address. It also logs aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, but does not record. which pages individual consumers access or visit.

**What other information do you collect?**

You can voluntarily chose to become a registered member. In doing so, we collect the name, e-mail address, city, state, zip code, date of birth, and certain voluntary personal information. We also collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and profile information volunteered by the consumer.

**What do you do with this information?**

The information we collect is used for internal review and to improve the content of our web page. The information we collect is not shared with other persons, companies, or organizations except when required by a law enforcement agency in the process of a criminal investigation.

**Do you use cookies?**

We use cookies to store certain information about registered members, visitors preferences, and to customize web page content based on the visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. All cookies are encrypted so they can’t be used by another website.

**What do you do with my personal information?**

All of the information collected remains confidential and is not shared with anyone other than the web site administrators. All of our web site administrators are instructed to maintain this confidentiality and are terminated if they are found in violation of this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information, but we do use it for marketing purposes. We send newsletters and other important system messages via email, but you have the option of not receiving these messages. You also have the option of which information is shared publicly in your profile. This information is used for internal marketing purposes and to provide services to our members.

**Do you partner with ad services which may collect information about me?**

While we may partner with some ad services from time to time, they will only have access to information you consent to provide them.

**What will happen if this privacy policy changes?**

Fromtime to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our web site and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically. Forthese new purposes, we will use only data collected from the time of the policy change forward.
